杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 在此之前，我们真的需要做任何有用的事情
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Before this is really
gonna do anything useful we need to
设置这些颜色。
actually set these colors, right.
这就是我们进入组件阴影的地方。
And this is where we get
into component shadowing.
所以《了不起的盖茨比》中的组成部分是一种
So component shadowing in
Gatsby is a method for
我们覆盖文件在另一个主题或插件。
us to override a file in another theme or
plugin.
不需要实际修改源代码，或者
Without actually needing to
modify the source code, or
潜入节点模块，或者完全退出所有代码。
dive into node modules, or
fully eject all the code.
所以我们可以选择一件我们想要改变的事情
So we can just pick one thing
that we want to change and
修改它，插件就会自动识别。
change it and
the plugin will pick that up.
所以要做到这一点，它的工作方式是我们可以针对我们想要改变的插件
So to do that the way that it works is we
can target the plugin we want to change so
Gatsby-plugin-theme-ui.
gatsby-plugin-theme-ui.
然后我们可以访问它的整个源文件夹。
And then inside of that we get
access to its whole source folder.
所以主题 UI 设置在他们把主题放在根目录的位置
So theme UI is set up where they
put the theme just at the root so
我们可以做 index.js。
we can do index.js.
要设置一个样式对象，我们只需导出一个对象。
And to set up a style object
we just export an object.
还有一些钥匙。
And there are some keys.
我们可以在 Theme-UI.com 上查看整个主题 UI 规范。
There's a whole Theme UI spec that
we can look at on theme-ui.com.
我不打算深入讨论这个，但是如果我们看看规格，我们可以看到那里
I'm not gonna get deep into this, but if
we look at the spec we can see that there
颜色，字体，字体大小，一系列你可以设置的东西。
are colors, fonts, font sizes,
a whole bunch of things that you can set.
如果你遵循这个规范，它的好处是
And if you follow this spec
the nice thing about it is that
任何遵循主题 UI 规范的主题都会尊重这些设置。
any theme following the Theme UI
spec will respect these settings.
因此，如果我设置一个主色，任何使用主题 UI 的网站都会尊重这个主色。
So if I set a primary color any site using
Theme UI will respect that primary color.
因此，如果我的网站导出一个主题对象所有的主题使用主题 UI 的
And so if my site exports a theme object
all of the themes using Theme UI that
会从我的主题 UI 对象中选取设置
are installed on my site will pick up
the settings from my Theme UI object
不需要我改变主题。
without me having to change
anything in the themes themselves.
所以这对我们来说真的真的很方便。
So this is really, really handy for us.
我要开始设置一些颜色。
And I'm just gonna set
up some colors to start.
所以让我们设置一个基本颜色，我们将它作为 rebeccapurple，因为这是
So let's set up a primary color, we’ll
make it rebeccapurple because this is
一个盖茨比的网站和盖茨比使用 rebeccapurple 作为品牌的颜色。
a Gatsby site and Gatsby uses
rebeccapurple as a brand color.
我们再来点靛蓝色,
We’ll do secondary of indigo,
我们可以设置一个柔和的灰色,
we can set up a muted color of gray,
字体颜色是紫色和 a。
a text color of purple and a.
白色背景。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Background of white.
这就足够让我们开始了。
And that’s good enough to get us started.
我们就从这里开始吧。
So let's just start the site here.
我们将做纱线工作区主题开发。
We'll do yarn workspace theme-dev develop.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 一旦这个问题得到解决
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: And
once this gets up and
运行我们可以看到它选择了我们的颜色。
running we can see that
it picked up our colors.